<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ashraf Jaffar</title>
    <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ashraf Jaffar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ashrafjfr.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Connect 👋</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Phone: +65 9088 3550
Email: ashraf.j@u.nus.edu
Telegram: @ashrafjfr
LinkedIn | GitHub | Instagram
Feel free to download my resume here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/skills/</guid>
      <description>Programming Languages ⌨️ C/C++ Java Python Assembly Language  Web Development 🖥️ HTML CSS Figma Adobe XD (UI Design / Prototyping)  Software Engineering 👨‍💻 Git GitHub Agile Framework Product Management  Hardware Development 🤖 Verilog Raspberry Pi ARM Cortex-M0+ Arduino LiDAR Real-Time Operating Systems  Creativity and More 🖌️ Adobe Creative Cloud (Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Premiere) Canva iMovie Photography Videography Social Media Marketing Copywriting Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Who Am I? 🤔My name is Ashraf and I’m a sophomore undergraduate currently pursuing a Computer Engineering Degree at the National University of Singapore (NUS). I am also an aspiring entrepreneur with a goal to create my own startup that can make the world a better place through innovative products for the masses!
I have a strong passion in analyzing companies and strategizing possible angles for upscaling businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>National University of Singapore (NUS) 🎓August 2020 - PresentBachelors of Engineering: Computer Engineering (Honours)   Relevant Courses Skills Learnt     Engineering Principles and Practice I &amp;amp; II C/C++, Robotics, Arduino, LiDAR, ROS, SLAM   Programming Methodology C, Vim, Linux, Bash   Data Structures and Algorithms C++, Basic Data Structures, Searching and Sorting Algorithms   Digital Design Verilog, Digital Logic, Digital Circuits   Computer Organisation Assembly Language, Computer Microarchitecture, Memory Systems   Software Engineering and Object-Oriented Programming Java, Git/GitHub, Agile Methodology, Scrum, User Stories, Product Testing   Real-Time Operating Systems (in progress) Embedded Systems, Microcontroller Programming, OS Concepts, Scheduling Algorithms   Signals and Systems (in progress) Fourier Transform, Sampling, Signal Reconstruction, Filtering   Design and Analysis of Algorithms (in progress) Framework for Algorithm Analysis    Raffles Institution (RI) 📚January 2012 - December 2017Singapore-Cambridge General Certificate of Education Advanced LevelScience Stream (Biology, Chemistry, Mathematics, Economics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiences</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/experiences/</guid>
      <description>Internship 🛠️SGInnovateProduct Management Intern (May 2021 - Aug 2021)
 Produced new UI/UX designs for in-house talent acquisition platform STARS Performed product testing on fixes, enhancements, and depployments Evaluated features of platform based on user feedback and develop recommendations for improvement Programmed Python scripts to evaluate talent scores depending on experiences and education Crafted a 70-page in-depth user manual to guide new hires and users on how to use in-house talent acquisiition platform  Project Coordinator Intern (Feb 2020 - Jun 2020)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashrafjfr.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>ConTechA Command Line Interface (CLI) application for managing computing-related contacts. Optimised for use on the CLI, ConTech allows you to seamlessly add, edit, view, list, search, and import your contacts. ConTech aims to improve your efficiency at work, be it by cutting down the time required to look up for various usernames when working with colleagues, or by importing hundreds of contacts with just one simple command.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
